Chloe Mac Mahon

Pretoria, Gauteng, South Africa



chloemacmahon@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/chloe-mac-mahon-2795aa1a9

Summary

I have experience in leaderships positions and feel comfortable taking the responsibility that a leadership position requires. In a leadership position I can comfortably express my thoughts and act as an advocate for those who struggle in this field. I have a passion for programming, problem solving and understanding the viewpoint of others to better solve intricate problems. I believe in continuous learning and constantly evolving to a changing working environment.

Experience



1 Tutor

North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit

Mar 2021 - Nov 2021 (9 months)

I assisted students with various questions they had as it relates to the Python programming language as well as the subject matter covered in CMPG 111. I also acted as a marker for this subject

Vacation Work Student

Psybergate (Pty) Ltd Jul 2021 - Jul 2021 (1 month)



North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit

Mar 2021 - Jul 2021 (5 months)

I assisted students with various problems they had as it relates to CMPG 221 and the Java programming language

Web Developer

Leap Innovation Technologies

Jul 2020 - May 2021 (11 months)

Designing websites for start up companies and also improving SEO scores and optimising website speed. Also designed and built various programs to assist with delivery and invoicing.



Tutor

North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit

Aug 2020 - Dec 2020 (5 months)

I assisted students with various problems relating to C++ programming and explained work as it relates to the CMPG 121



North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit

Sep 2020 - Nov 2020 (3 months)

Helping first-year students understand the basics of User Interface Development

Tutor

North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit

Feb 2020 - Jun 2020 (5 months)

I assisted students with various queries they had as it relates to the Python programming language and various questions they had in regards to the CMPG 111 subject

Education

North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit

BSc , Information Technology 2019 - 2021

Licenses & Certifications

G The fundamentals of Digital Marketing - Google R2F38FGN3

- Short Course on Drawing Art North West University
- HX CS50L: CS50 for Lawyers HarvardX 58dd8d8d261541e8b9e6dcb7a3f97e50
- HX CS50: Introduction to Computer Science HarvardX

4a8467e96f4a4184894b4ad70888691e

Data Science for Everyone - DataCamp 16,424,598

- Introduction to Python DataCamp 16,640,603
- Intermediate Python DataCamp 16,710,061
- Python Data Science Toolbox (Part 1) DataCamp
- Python (basic) HackerRank

- Git IBM
- Agile Intro IBM
- Web Development IBM
- BM API IBM
- Clean code Udemy
 UC-93c260f2-fe49-4777-8845-c0d9269da199
- Mastering thymeleaf with spring boot Udemy

Skills

Java • C++ • Python (Programming Language) • C# • C (Programming Language)

Honors & Awards

DIRISA Datathon 4th place - DIRISA
Jul 2021